{
  "name": "Spanish",
  "cards": [
    {
      "question": "One",
      "answer": "Uno"
    },
    {
      "question": "Two",
      "answer": "dos"
    },
    {
      "question": "Three",
      "answer": "tres"
    },
    {
      "question": "Four",
      "answer": "cuatro"
    },
    {
      "question": "Five",
      "answer": "cinco"
    },
    {
      "question": "Six",
      "answer": "seis"
    },
    {
      "question": "Seven",
      "answer": "siete"
    },
    {
      "question": "Eight",
      "answer": "Ocho"
    },
    {
      "question": "Nine",
      "answer": "Nueve"
    },
    {
      "question": "Ten",
      "answer": "Diez"
    },
    {
      "question": "Zero",
      "answer": "Cero"
    }
  ]
}